<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>رادیو خط فرمان</title>
    <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on رادیو خط فرمان</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fa-ir</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 04:10:01 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://khatefarman.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Title</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/template/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 04:10:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/template/</guid>
      <description>لورم ایپسوم متن ساختگی با تولید سادگی نامفهوم از صنعت چاپ و با استفاده از طراحان گرافیک است. چاپگرها و متون بلکه روزنامه و مجله در ستون و سطرآنچنان که لازم است و برای شرایط فعلی تکنولوژی مورد نیاز و کاربردهای متنوع با هدف بهبود ابزارهای کاربردی می باشد. کتابهای زیادی در شصت و سه درصد گذشته، حال و آینده شناخت فراوان جامعه و متخصصان را می طلبد تا با نرم افزارها شناخت بیشتری را برای طراحان رایانه ای علی الخصوص طراحان خلاقی و فرهنگ پیشرو در زبان فارسی ایجاد کرد.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelly Dixon</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/guest/template/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 09:12:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/guest/template/</guid>
      <description>molestias adipisci quia esse. ex qui ipsam eveniet. in velit et pariatur molestiae harum! repudiandae fugit eos. itaque aut incidunt quo et ipsum ut. voluptatibus totam corporis itaque id sit. sunt modi sed blanditiis et alias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>راه‌های ارتباط</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 15:19:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Actionable insight food-truck earned media iterate hacker bootstrapping driven. Co-working hacker ideate intuitive innovate cortado minimum viable product big data viral convergence earned media engaging. Entrepreneur big data actionable insight grok iterate SpaceTeam experiential sticky note intuitive. Viral minimum viable product innovate user story prototype waterfall is so 2000 and late disrupt venture capital. Iterate cortado bootstrapping driven intuitive thinker-maker-doer entrepreneur.
Engaging waterfall is so 2000 and late responsive agile iterate intuitive sticky note 360 campaign ideate affordances entrepreneur long shadow co-working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>books</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 15:18:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/books/</guid>
      <description>Actionable insight food-truck earned media iterate hacker bootstrapping driven. Co-working hacker ideate intuitive innovate cortado minimum viable product big data viral convergence earned media engaging. Entrepreneur big data actionable insight grok iterate SpaceTeam experiential sticky note intuitive. Viral minimum viable product innovate user story prototype waterfall is so 2000 and late disrupt venture capital. Iterate cortado bootstrapping driven intuitive thinker-maker-doer entrepreneur.
Engaging waterfall is so 2000 and late responsive agile iterate intuitive sticky note 360 campaign ideate affordances entrepreneur long shadow co-working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>امیرحسین گودرزی</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/host/amir/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 20:55:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/host/amir/</guid>
      <description>Matt Stratton is a solutions architect at Chef, where he demonstrates how Chef’s automation platform provides speed and flexibility to clients’ infrastructure. He is devoted to concepts like Continuous Delivery and Infrastructure as Code, and his license plate actually says “DevOps”. He lives in Chicago and has an unhealthy obsession with Doctor Who, Firefly, and Game of Thrones. And whiskey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>بهروز حسن‌بیگی</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/host/behrooz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 20:55:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/host/behrooz/</guid>
      <description>Bridget Kromhout is a Principal Cloud Developer Advocate at Microsoft. Her CS degree emphasis was in theory, but she now deals with the concrete (if &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; can be considered tangible). After 15 years as an operations engineer, she traded being on call for being on a plane. A frequent speaker and program committee member for tech conferences, she leads the devopsdays organization globally and the devops community at home in Minneapolis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>حسین فرمانی</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/host/hossein/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 20:55:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/host/hossein/</guid>
      <description>حسین فرمانی هستم یک علاقه مند به دنیای باینری از نوع آزادش و تمام اتفاقاتی که توش ممکنه بیفته. فرمانی صدام میکنند ولی صمیمی تر ها با حسین راحت تر هستن. توی دانشگاه مهندسی کامپیوتر گرایش نرم افزار خوندم از اونجایی که از سه چهار سالگی تو خونمون کامپیوتر داشتم با کامپیوتر بزرگ شدم و تقریبا بخش عمده ای از عمرم رو با کامپیوتر سرگرم بودم و خوب علاقم به این مورد باعث شد که در تمام این سال هایی که بزرگتر میشدم این عشق پا برجا بمونه و روز به روز بیشتر و بیشتر درگیرش باشم تا امروز که با این عشق کسب درآمد و گذران زندگی میکنم.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>درباره پادکست</title>
      <link>https://khatefarman.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 02:11:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khatefarman.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>